[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iowa"]}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 4, "question": "Are attack ads the price of admission in politics?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "attack", "ads", "the", "price", "of", "admission", "in", "politics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 5, "answer": "I believe the people of Iowa are smart enough that they can see the difference between somebody who's trying to help the country and somebody who is simply running a negative campaign.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "believe", "the", "people", "of", "Iowa", "are", "smart", "enough", "that", "they", "can", "see", "the", "difference", "between", "somebody", "who", "'s", "trying", "to", "help", "the", "country", "and", "somebody", "who", "is", "simply", "running", "a", "negative", "campaign", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "Would you agree?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "agree", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Well, it's working for a variety of reasons, Piers, but what I'd satisfy is this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "working", "for", "a", "variety", "of", "reasons", ",", "Piers", ",", "but", "what", "I", "'d", "satisfy", "is", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Newt"]}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "What's your reading of these fluctuations?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "reading", "of", "these", "fluctuations", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Well, there's durability in Newt's numbers based on what you've shown.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "durability", "in", "Newt", "'s", "numbers", "based", "on", "what", "you", "'ve", "shown", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Yes, it's, as I said, lacerating, but it also has the benefit of being factually correct, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", ",", "as", "I", "said", ",", "lacerating", ",", "but", "it", "also", "has", "the", "benefit", "of", "being", "factually", "correct", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Not all of it.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "all", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "Would you dispute any of the details?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "dispute", "any", "of", "the", "details", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Not all of it.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "all", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "Jump in there?", "question_tokens": ["Jump", "in", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "Sure, so Governor.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", ",", "so", "Governor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "TO", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "What is Newt Gingrich's view of this apparently intransigent position by the Republicans which is causing endless grief to everybody?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "Newt", "Gingrich", "'s", "view", "of", "this", "apparently", "intransigent", "position", "by", "the", "Republicans", "which", "is", "causing", "endless", "grief", "to", "everybody", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "Well, if anybody wants to know Newt's views on anything go to Newt.org.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "anybody", "wants", "to", "know", "Newt", "'s", "views", "on", "anything", "go", "to", "Newt.org", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "Isn't it time for a president who looks like a 1970s game show host?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "time", "for", "a", "president", "who", "looks", "like", "a", "1970s", "game", "show", "host", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1970s"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "Isn't part of the problem for Mitt Romney is that people do look at him and think '70s game show host?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "part", "of", "the", "problem", "for", "Mitt", "Romney", "is", "that", "people", "do", "look", "at", "him", "and", "think", "'70s", "game", "show", "host", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Well, you know, first of all, none of these candidates are perfect.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "none", "of", "these", "candidates", "are", "perfect", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "Governor Pawlenty, we really don't want to have the debate, do we, about which candidate in this field has changed their mind?", "question_tokens": ["Governor", "Pawlenty", ",", "we", "really", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "have", "the", "debate", ",", "do", "we", ",", "about", "which", "candidate", "in", "this", "field", "has", "changed", "their", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Pawlenty"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Let me start with you, Mary Matalin, I mean is it too late for Sarah Palin?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "start", "with", "you", ",", "Mary", "Matalin", ",", "I", "mean", "is", "it", "too", "late", "for", "Sarah", "Palin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary Matalin", "Sarah Palin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Technically is it too late?", "question_tokens": ["Technically", "is", "it", "too", "late", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "Not technically.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "technically", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin"]}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "I mean is the field still open or are they in the end going to choose now from what would appear to be a narrowing field?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "is", "the", "field", "still", "open", "or", "are", "they", "in", "the", "end", "going", "to", "choose", "now", "from", "what", "would", "appear", "to", "be", "a", "narrowing", "field", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Well, I would say this about Sarah Palin.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "say", "this", "about", "Sarah", "Palin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ron Paul"], "LOCATION": ["Iowa"]}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "Knowing the lay of the land there, how do you see things panning out in the next couple of weeks?", "question_tokens": ["Knowing", "the", "lay", "of", "the", "land", "there", ",", "how", "do", "you", "see", "things", "panning", "out", "in", "the", "next", "couple", "of", "weeks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "I think that we are on a collision course with a Ron Paul victory in the Iowa caucuses.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "we", "are", "on", "a", "collision", "course", "with", "a", "Ron", "Paul", "victory", "in", "the", "Iowa", "caucuses", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "I mean the way this has been structured now this year coming up with New York and California, a song coming much later, this process could go on for months and months and months with the leadership changing quite dramatically, couldn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "the", "way", "this", "has", "been", "structured", "now", "this", "year", "coming", "up", "with", "New", "York", "and", "California", ",", "a", "song", "coming", "much", "later", ",", "this", "process", "could", "go", "on", "for", "months", "and", "months", "and", "months", "with", "the", "leadership", "changing", "quite", "dramatically", ",", "could", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "RB", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York", "California"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "Why is that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "I think it's really the words you used, character.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "really", "the", "words", "you", "used", ",", "character", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "MD", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "And what makes him special?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "makes", "him", "special", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "Well, what makes him special is his will to win, his drive, his desire.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "makes", "him", "special", "is", "his", "will", "to", "win", ",", "his", "drive", ",", "his", "desire", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "What is wrong with a God-fearing guy who goes out, works hard, you know, does his job but believes in God and sends a positive message?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "wrong", "with", "a", "God-fearing", "guy", "who", "goes", "out", ",", "works", "hard", ",", "you", "know", ",", "does", "his", "job", "but", "believes", "in", "God", "and", "sends", "a", "positive", "message", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RP", ",", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "HITAKER: Right.", "answer_tokens": ["HITAKER", ":", "Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "I mean, am I wrong about that or is that a particular talent that he has that is putting him slightly above the others at the moment?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "am", "I", "wrong", "about", "that", "or", "is", "that", "a", "particular", "talent", "that", "he", "has", "that", "is", "putting", "him", "slightly", "above", "the", "others", "at", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Well, because of his skill set and his athleticism, he can get away from the rush and can he buy time and he does get more time to throw than a lot of other quarterbacks, but he's still learning the position and that's what people have to understand.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "because", "of", "his", "skill", "set", "and", "his", "athleticism", ",", "he", "can", "get", "away", "from", "the", "rush", "and", "can", "he", "buy", "time", "and", "he", "does", "get", "more", "time", "to", "throw", "than", "a", "lot", "of", "other", "quarterbacks", ",", "but", "he", "'s", "still", "learning", "the", "position", "and", "that", "'s", "what", "people", "have", "to", "understand", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "OK?", "question_tokens": ["OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "I love you, too.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "you", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "But, just take it down a notch, will you, buddy?", "question_tokens": ["But", ",", "just", "take", "it", "down", "a", "notch", ",", "will", "you", ",", "buddy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Yes, Lord, whatever you command.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "Lord", ",", "whatever", "you", "command", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "I mean, if you're a young person watching football right now, Tebow magic isn't going to do you any harm, is it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "if", "you", "'re", "a", "young", "person", "watching", "football", "right", "now", ",", "Tebow", "magic", "is", "n't", "going", "to", "do", "you", "any", "harm", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "It's really not.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "really", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tebow"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "JJR", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "How's he going to do?", "question_tokens": ["How", "'s", "he", "going", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Well, they need one more win to get into the playoffs, and I know Tim wants to deliver that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "need", "one", "more", "win", "to", "get", "into", "the", "playoffs", ",", "and", "I", "know", "Tim", "wants", "to", "deliver", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "How far is he going to go, do you think, and how will he deal with it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "far", "is", "he", "going", "to", "go", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "and", "how", "will", "he", "deal", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "I think he'll deal with it great.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'ll", "deal", "with", "it", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "I mean, that's what's making him the sort of people's hero, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "that", "'s", "what", "'s", "making", "him", "the", "sort", "of", "people", "'s", "hero", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "POS", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "It is, but I think that really has to do with his faith, too.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", ",", "but", "I", "think", "that", "really", "has", "to", "do", "with", "his", "faith", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Am I know doing the Tebow?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "know", "doing", "the", "Tebow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "You are.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tebow"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 457, "question": "And what does this bring me?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "does", "this", "bring", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Well, I --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "What's the matter now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "matter", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Would you wait.", "answer_tokens": ["Would", "you", "wait", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "Do you get as much of a thrill out of the very, by comparison, very boring process of making a movie?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "get", "as", "much", "of", "a", "thrill", "out", "of", "the", "very", ",", "by", "comparison", ",", "very", "boring", "process", "of", "making", "a", "movie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "Well, first of all, thank you very much.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "thank", "you", "very", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Are you prepared to reveal number of press-ups and number of stomach crunches you can achieve?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "prepared", "to", "reveal", "number", "of", "press-ups", "and", "number", "of", "stomach", "crunches", "you", "can", "achieve", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Even if I tell you what I -- we get in the ring and I do boxing with him --", "answer_tokens": ["Even", "if", "I", "tell", "you", "what", "I", "--", "we", "get", "in", "the", "ring", "and", "I", "do", "boxing", "with", "him", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Do you, really?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", ",", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "And that's where I think you and I differ.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "that", "'s", "where", "I", "think", "you", "and", "I", "differ", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "Everything you know about me, Kenneth, would you imagine I'm a fair fighter?", "question_tokens": ["Everything", "you", "know", "about", "me", ",", "Kenneth", ",", "would", "you", "imagine", "I", "'m", "a", "fair", "fighter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "I'd be pretty careful where the gloves go.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "be", "pretty", "careful", "where", "the", "gloves", "go", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kenneth"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Olivier"]}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", ",", "CC", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Who has been, pound for pound, the greatest actor that you've ever seen in action?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "has", "been", ",", "pound", "for", "pound", ",", "the", "greatest", "actor", "that", "you", "'ve", "ever", "seen", "in", "action", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "Well, I have to say, I'm sorry it's a bit of a boring answer given what we're kind of talking about, but Olivier, I think, really does take some beating.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "to", "say", ",", "I", "'m", "sorry", "it", "'s", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "boring", "answer", "given", "what", "we", "'re", "kind", "of", "talking", "about", ",", "but", "Olivier", ",", "I", "think", ",", "really", "does", "take", "some", "beating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "I mean, do you have the old Peter's friends, gang all get together?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "have", "the", "old", "Peter", "'s", "friends", ",", "gang", "all", "get", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "Well, I haven't done much of that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "n't", "done", "much", "of", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Peter"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle Williams", "Marilyn"]}, "docId": "111220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "VB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "``", "JJ", "TO", ",", "''", ":", "NN", ":", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "VBG", ",", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "Who's the one you'd choose for your last, ever role?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "the", "one", "you", "'d", "choose", "for", "your", "last", ",", "ever", "role", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Oh, wow, you put me on the spot there, because I'm going to say, and please don't hate me for this being an obvious answer, but I just watched Michelle Williams, \"Close to,\" (ph), across the last picture we made from the most unlikely of the, this sort of fragile and petite, seeming, beautiful young woman, seemed to expand in the makeup chair as she filled out the curves of Marilyn, she found the voice, she occupied the face, the hair, the walk, which wasn't so much of a walk as a float, a shimmy through the movie.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "wow", ",", "you", "put", "me", "on", "the", "spot", "there", ",", "because", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "say", ",", "and", "please", "do", "n't", "hate", "me", "for", "this", "being", "an", "obvious", "answer", ",", "but", "I", "just", "watched", "Michelle", "Williams", ",", "``", "Close", "to", ",", "''", "(", "ph", ")", ",", "across", "the", "last", "picture", "we", "made", "from", "the", "most", "unlikely", "of", "the", ",", "this", "sort", "of", "fragile", "and", "petite", ",", "seeming", ",", "beautiful", "young", "woman", ",", "seemed", "to", "expand", "in", "the", "makeup", "chair", "as", "she", "filled", "out", "the", "curves", "of", "Marilyn", ",", "she", "found", "the", "voice", ",", "she", "occupied", "the", "face", ",", "the", "hair", ",", "the", "walk", ",", "which", "was", "n't", "so", "much", "of", "a", "walk", "as", "a", "float", ",", "a", "shimmy", "through", "the", "movie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]